<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quick Pick</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="title_activity_starter">StarterActivity</string>
    <string name="about">The main idea behind this project has risen from our very own experience. Cooking is an art form which everyone won’t be able to work on successfully at a very initial stage. For a beginner, it is really a tough task to make a dish without having it burned or causing harm to themselves. Consider the case of a student who is not skilled enough as he or she has never got a chance to cook something by themselves. Due to their lack of experience and improper knowledge to make a dish, it seems difficult. And, at times they’re even some cases where they do want to cook but they are not aware of what ingredients they require. Also, they’re times where they do have the required ingredients but are unable to work as they’re unaware of its procedure. Due to this problem, one tends to find peace in having instant food. Most of the people who are not skilled to cook a dish find pleasure in ordering a pizza online, getting food from drive ins. Some people make it possible by cooking instant ready-made food in which they just put hot water and the food is ready as in the case of cup noodles. Some people use frozen food from the markets to make their food which is even not good for health.
In all the cases mentioned above, there are high chances of not providing your body with all the nutrients and vitamins it requires on a daily-basis. Consider any generation, be it young or old, it is very important for everyone to put some effort and take healthy and hygienic food for they could be away from all the infections and weaknesses. With the changing weather, a human’s body must be provided with all the types of carbohydrates, proteins, vitamins and minerals to defend itself from easy attacks of flu, cold and even fever.  And this can only happen when one takes in regular diet and eats healthy organic food.\n\n
There are also few case scenarios, where one wants to cook food but due to work pressure and stress that they face in life, they get used to the instant food available in the market. Also, when one is trying to balance both work and study at the same time, it gets difficult to reach home being tired and then put an effort to make food by watching videos online or finding recipes by surfing online. As an international student, staying miles away from home, with the change in the type of food that they usually consume, one does not know to handle it well in terms of food in-take. But there is a solution to all these problems which is the main objective of our project, Quick Pick. Our application, Quick Pick helps the customer mainly bachelor students to make food with the limited number of ingredients they have in the kitchen. Based on the ingredients they have, they can make food accordingly. The application becomes easy to use as they get to select ingredients they have in their kitchen and search for all the dishes or recipes that can be prepared based on those limited number of ingredients. They can select a recipe of their choice that is based on the available ingredients at their side and can follow the procedure or steps that is required to make that particular dish. The procedure or process to make a dish that is selected by user is given with just a click away on the application. This way, it becomes easy for a student or anyone who is new to making food to prepare food easily with the available list of items that they have in the kitchen within no time. After all, we all need food to sustain ourselves and stay alive.
</string>
</resources>
